

CONTACT ME

devon.r.morden@gmail.com dmlearningdesign.com 2156 Bollinger Mill Rd. Finksburg, MD 20148 717.686.3663

I am a professional with a wide breadth of experience. An avid 'deep-diver' Regardless of topic, I am a life-long learner and a skilled and candid communicator. I have experience in Education, Instructional Design, Web Design, Digital Marketing, and Academia.

SKILLS

Web Design & Digital Marketing

- HTML intermediate
- CSS intermediate
- JavaScript basic
- Sass basic
- NodelS basic
- Git & GitHub
- WCAG compliance
- SEO
- PPC Google, Facebook, LinkedIn
- Social Media Management

Instructional Design

- ADDIE & SAM
- UbD/Backwards Design
- Andragogy
- UX/UI
- Articulate 360
- Canvas
- MS Office Suite
- MS Project
- Google Suite
- Adobe Illustrator & Photoshop
- Visual Studio Code

SOFT SKILLS

- Project Management -Waterfall & Agile
- Challenging Conversations
- Leadership Communication
- Active Listening
- Diversity, Equity, Inclusion, and Justice

EDUCATION

Udacity, Udemy, LinkedIn Learning, Free Code Camp

Various certificates and courses including coding, web development, digital marketing, project management, instructional design, and graphic design

Oregon State University; E-Learning and Instructional Design Certificate (2021-2022)

Ursinus College; K-12 Teaching Certificate (2013-2014); GPA 3.87

Villanova University; Classics MA (incomplete) (2012); GPA 3.44

University of Cambridge; Philology & Indo-European Linguistics MPhil (2011-2012); Overall: 2.1, Thesis: 1st

Ursinus College; Classics (Dist. Honors) & Linguistics BA (2007-2011); Summa cum Laude; GPA 3.89

WORK EXPERIENCE

Biddable Marketing Coordinator

Freeman's Auction; December 2021 - present

- Brought our Google Ads campaigns from nearly zero conversions per month to approximately 25 to 100 conversions per month and reduced our bounce rate from nearly 100% to under 50%
- Worked with department specialists to develop effective keywords and targeting
- Revived our nearly defunct Artist biography with the assistance of Streambid, which will have significant SEO benefits once complete
- Working on our website's accessibility to meet WCAG and 508 compliance
- Working to develop SEO-friendly department pages
- Advising on the options for UX research and a new website

Social Media Coordinator

Freeman's Auction; March 2021 - December 2021

- Increased social media followers and engagement by hundreds
- Worked with department specialists and our Brand Manager to develop relevant and engaging social media content
- Revived our Google Ads account

Marketing Assistant

Freeman's Auction; March 2020 - March 2021

- Assisted with marketing tasks as needed
- Facilitated the posting of social media content

Middle School Latin Teacher

The Bryn Mawr School for Girls; August 2014 - July 2019

- Effectively managed students, developed three year-long curricula each year, planned engaging daily learning experiences, analyzed student data and implemented approapriate changes.
- Planned and executed extracurricular learning experiences

Middle School Diversity Coordinator

The Bryn Mawr School for Girls; February 2015 - December 2018

- Lead the project to develop a K-12 diversity curriculum
- Lead professional development experiences to engage and educate colleagues
- Addressed issues of diversity as they arose between faculty and students
- Worked with the parents' association to gain acceptance of the new curriculum